Guide to the American political campaigns miscellany, 1868-2016
American political campaigns miscellany
- Series V. Buttons
  - (Not Located), 6477.BT0036; Items: (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0037; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "President Nixon. Now More Than Ever" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0038; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Vandenberg For President" Campaign Button, ca. 1940; 6477.BT0039; Items: 1 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Vandenberg, Arthur H.
    Election: 1940
  - "Get On The Van Wagon" Campaign Button, ca. 1940; 6477.BT0040; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Vandenberg" Campaign Button, ca. 1940; 6477.BT0041; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Vandenberg" (Rectangular Cardboard Badge), ca.1940; 6477.BT0042; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Vote Socialist Workers Camejo For President (Campaign Button), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0043; Items: 1 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Camejo, Peter
    Party: Socialist Workers
  - "Vote Socialist Workers Reid For Vice President" (Campaign Button), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0044; Items: 1 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Reid, Willie Mae
  - "Rockefeller For Governor'" Photographic Campaign Button, 1958-1970; 6477.BT0045; Items: 5 (Box 3)
    Election: 1958; 1962; 1966; 1970
  - "My Man Humphrey" Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0046; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - Joe Talbot U.S. Senate Campaign Button, ca. 1950; 6477.BT0047; Items: 1 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Talbot, Joseph E.
  - "For Congress "Sherry" Campaign Button, n/a; 6477.BT0048; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Gene McCarthy" Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0049; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "McCarthy For President" Campaign Button White with Blue Letters, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0050; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "McCarthy For President" Campaign Button Green with White Letters, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0051; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "If I Were 21 I'd Vote For Barry" Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0052; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Goldwater Miller in '64" Campaign Button, 1964; 6477.BT0053; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - ""Goldwater in 64" Photographic Campaign Button, 1964; 6477.BT0054; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Goldwater Miller" Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0055; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Let's Put An Honest Man In The White House" Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0056; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - "Nixon 72" Campaign Button, 1972; 6477.BT0057; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "I'm For Nixon In '72" Campaign Button, 1972; 6477.BT0058; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "All The Way With Adlai" 2-Way Photo/Type Campaign Button, ca. 1952-1956; 6477.BT0059; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "McGovern" Campaign Button, ca. 1972; 6477.BT0060; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - "Humphrey-Muskie" Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0061; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - IKE-Nixon Campaign Button, ca. 1952-1956; 6477.BT0062; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - Re-Elect Ives Senator, n/a; 6477.BT0063; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: Ives, Irving M.
  - We [Heart] Matt Button, ca. 1982; 6477.BT0064; Items: 1 (Box 4)
    Candidate: MCHugh, Matthew
  - Courtney Crawford Nyack (Rectangular Button), n/a; 6477.BT0065; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - Johnson-Humphrey Buttons, 1964; 6477.BT0066; Items: 3 (Box 4)
  - Goldwater-Miller Lapel Tabs (Rectangular, gold, with blue letters), 1964; 6477.BT0067; Items: 5 (Box 4)
  - Goldwater Miller GOParty 1964Campaign Buttons, 1964; 6477.BT0068; Items: 2 (Box 4)
  - Keep Keating New York's Own Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0069; Items: 1 (Box 4)
  - Robison Is My Congressman Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0070; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Robison Lapel Tab, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0071; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Kennedy Lapel Tab (Red letters on White background), ca. 1962; 6477.BT0072; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Election: 1962
  - White Plastic Elephant Pin with G.O.P. in Red Letters, n/a; 6477.BT0073; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Experience Counts Vote Nixon-Lodge (Portrait Lenticular Button), ca. 1960; 6477.BT0074; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Kennedy Lapel Tabs (Blue letters on White background), ca. 1960; 6477.BT0075; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Kennedy For President Campaign Button, ca. 1960; 6477.BT0076; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Nixon Lodge Campaign Buttons and Lapel Pins, ca. 1960; 6477.BT0077; Items: 5 (Box 5)
  - Senator Goodell (Two Campaign Buttons and Two Lapel Tabs), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0078; Items: 4 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Goodell, Charles E.
  - Lefkowitz Attorney General Campaign Buttons, ca. 1970; 6477.BT0079; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Rockefeller Photograph (Button), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0080; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Independents For Rockefeller Campaign Buttons, ca. 1970; 6477.BT0081; Items: 2 (Box 5)
    Party: Independent; Republican
  - Campaign Buttons For Various New York State Candidates, ca. 1970; 6477.BT0082; Items: 6 (Box 3)
    Candidate: Various
  - Lt. Gov. Wilson (Lapel Tabs), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0083; Items: 2 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Wilson, Malcolm
  - Rocky Puts It Together(Campaign Buttons), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0084; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Rockefeller He's Done a Lot. He'll Do More (Campaign Buttons), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0085; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Rockefeller Campaign Buttons (White with Blue Stripes), ca. 1970; 6477.BT0086; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Rockefeller Lapel Tab, ca. 1970; 6477.BT0087; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Trust Humphrey Campaign Buttons, 1968; 6477.BT0088; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Javits Campaign Buttons, 1968; 6477.BT0089; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Humphrey-Muskie Campaign Button, 1968; 6477.BT0090; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Re-Elect Congressman Stratton Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0091; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Stratton, Samuel S.
  - Symington For President Campaign Button, ca. 1960; 6477.BT0092; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Symington, Stuart
  - Howard Samuels For Governor Campaign Buttons, ca. 1970; 6477.BT0093; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - I Give TPEL Do You (Buttons), n/a; 6477.BT0094; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Johnson for President (Large Portrait Campaign Button), ca. 1964; 6477.BT0095; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - USA Loves LBJ Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0096; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - LBJ HHH For the U.S.A. Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0097; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - America Needs Johnson Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0098; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - If I Were 21 I'd Vote For Johnson Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0099; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - Johnson for President Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0100; Items: 1 (Box 3)
  - Labor For Johnson For Labor Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0101; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Republicans For Johnson Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0102; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Johnson Lapel Tab, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0103; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Johnson Humphrey Photographic Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0104; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Johnson And Humphrey Campaign Button, ca. 1964; 6477.BT0105; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Humphrey-Muskie Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0106; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Humphrey-Muskie Lapel Tab, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0107; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - H.H.H. Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0108; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Humphrey Campaign Button (White signature on blue background), ca. 1968; 6477.BT0109; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Humphrey For President Campaign Button, ca. 1968; 6477.BT0110; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - McHugh Campaign Button (Red and Orange), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0111; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - McHugh For Congress Campaign Button (Dark Blue and White), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0112; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Canvasser McHugh For Congress Campaign Button, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0113; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Gary Lee For Assembly Campaign Button, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0114; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Do You Want A Nut In The White House? Anti-Carter Campaign Button, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0115; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - President Ford Campaign Button (White letters on Red), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0116; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - President Ford Campaign Button (White letters on Blue), ca. 1976; 6477.BT0117; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Ford Dole Campaign Button, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0118; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Re-Elect Carter Mondale Campaign Button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0119; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Reagan Bush '85 Campaign Button, 1984; 6477.BT0120; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - The Time Is Now: Reagan Bush Campaign Button, 1980; 6477.BT0121; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Siegel For State Senate Campaign Button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0122; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Congressman Gary Lee Campaign Button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0123; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Bill Smith State Senator Campaign Button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0124; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Senator Javits Campaign Button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0125; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Reagan For President Campaign Button, 1980; 6477.BT0126; Items: 2 (Box 5)
  - Republican For A Better Michigan Campaign Button, n/a; 6477.BT0127; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Clinton Team Lapel Pin (Collectable Limited Edition, on Card), ca. 1996; 6477.BT0128; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Clinton, Bill
    Election: 1996
  - Mondale Ferraro Now Campaign Button (Green with white letters), ca. 1984; 6477.BT0129; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Mondale Ferraro Campaign Button (Red, White & Blue, 1-1/4"), ca. 1984; 6477.BT0130; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Mondale Ferraro Campaign Button (Red, White & Blue, 2-1/4"), ca. 1984; 6477.BT0131; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Ferraro For Vice-President Campaign Button, ca. 1984; 6477.BT0132; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Ferraro, Geraldine
  - Connie Cook For Congress Campaign Button, ca. 1984; 6477.BT0133; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Cook, Constance
  - Anderson Of Illinois for President Campaign button, ca. 1980; 6477.BT0134; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Anderson, John
  - Duryea For Governor Campaign Button, ca. 1978; 6477.BT0135; Items: 2 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Duryea, Perry
    Election: 1978
  - Hoover Campaign Button, ca. 1932; 6477.BT0136; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Hoover, Herbert
    Election: 1932
  - Landon Knox Campaign Button, ca. 1936; 6477.BT0137; Items: 1 (Box 5)
    Candidate: Landon, Alfred M.
  - Mark For Mayor Campaign Button, n/a; 6477.BT0138; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - For Governor McCall/Mehiel For Lieutenant Governor Campaign Button, ca. 2002; 6477.BT0139; Items: 1 (Box 5)
  - Nixon/Lodge Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0140; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Nixon, Richard M. and Henry Cabot Lodge
    Election: n.d.
  - I'm for Nixon Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0141; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - McCarthy Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0142; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: McCarthy, Eugene
    Election: [1968]
  - McGovern/Shriver Presidential Campaign Button, 1972; 6477.BT0143; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: McGovern, George and Sargent Shriver
  - Carter/Mondale Presidential Campaign Button, 1980; 6477.BT0144; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Carter, Jimmy and Walter Mondale
  - Go Perot Campaign Buttons, 1992 or 1996; 6477.BT0145; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Go Perot Campaign Buttons, 1992 or 1996; 6477.BT0146; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - Mondale's Got The Beef Campaign Button, [1984?]; 6477.BT0147; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Election: [1984]
  - Mondale/Ferraro Presidential Campaign Button, 1984; 6477.BT0148; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0149; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Dukakis, Michael and Lloyd Bentsen
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0150; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0151; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0152; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0153; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0154; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0155; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - "It's Time to Say Dukakis/Bentsen Yes" Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0156; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - "It's Time to Say Dukakis/Bentsen Yes" Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0157; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0158; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis for President 1988 Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0159; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - 1988 Dukakis for President Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0160; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Mike Dukakis for President '88 Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0161; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - Michael Dukakis for President 1988 Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0162; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Governor Michael Dukakis for President 1988 Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0163; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Democratic Integrity Dukakis in 1988 Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0164; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Democratic Integrity Dukakis in 1988 Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0165; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - The Tradition Lives On! Dukakis/Kennedy Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0166; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - America Needs Dukakis Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0167; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - I Like Mike Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0168; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Duke! Duke! Duke! Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0169; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - We're With the Duke Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0170; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Betnsen for Vice President in 1988 Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0171; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Kitty Dukakis for First Lady Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0172; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Democratic National Convention/Atlanta 1988 Button, 1988; 6477.BT0173; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - Democratic National Convention/Atlanta '88/July 18-21,1988 Button, 1988; 6477.BT0174; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Atlanta '88/Democratic National ConventionJuly 18-21, 1988Button, 1988; 6477.BT0175; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Atlanta '88/July 18-21, 1988/Democratic National Convention Button, 1988; 6477.BT0176; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Jesse Jackson for President Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0177; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Jesse Jackson '88 Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0178; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - 88 Jesse/Jesse/88 Jesse 88/Jesse/Jesse 88 Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0179; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Clinton/Gore Presidential Campaign Button, 1992 or 1996; 6477.BT0180; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Clinton, William Jefferson and Al Gore
  - Clinton/Gore Presidential Campaign Button, 1992 or 1996; 6477.BT0181; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Clinton/Gore Election '96 Starts Now Presidential Campaign Button, 1996; 6477.BT0182; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Bill Clinton for President 1992 Campaign Button, 1992; 6477.BT0183; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Re-elect Bill & Take Back The Hill Presidential Campaign Button, 1996; 6477.BT0184; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - Farmers for Dean Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0185; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Dean, Howard
  - Kerry/Edwards/JOHNKERRY.COM Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0186; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Clark for President 04/www.clark04.com Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0187; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Clark, Wesley K.
  - Jeff Miller for Congress/www.jeffmiller2004.com Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0188; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Miller, Jeff
  - Commission on Presidential Debates/Presidential Debate/October 8, 2004/Washington University in St. Louis Button, 2004; 6477.BT0189; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Don't Blame Me I Voted Libertarian/800-ELECT-US Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0190; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Party: Libertarian
  - The Libertarian Party/Pro-Choice ON EVERYTHING/800-Elect-Us Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0191; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: n.d.
  - No Newts is Good Newts [Gingrich], Americans for Democratic Action, Campaign Button, n.d.; 6477.BT0192; Items: 2 (Box 21)
  - HINCHEY=CHOICE Campaign Button, 1992-2006; 6477.BT0193; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Hinchey, Maurice
    Election: 1992-2006
  - BU[LL]SH[IT] Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0194; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Like Father Like Son/One Term And You're Done Presidentisl Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0195; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - OH NO/NOT AGAIN! Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0196; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - 1000 Points of Light/1 Dim Bulb Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0197; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - LIAR LIAR/PANTS ON FIRE! Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0198; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - A COUNTY IN TEXAS/IS MISSING IT'S IDIOT Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0199; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - BUSH CHENEY '04/Leave No Billionaire Behind Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0200; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Bush, George and Richard Cheney
  - ABB Anybody But Bush Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0201; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - THE NEW 2004 NO C.A.R.B. DIET/NO CHENEY/NO ASHCROFT/NO RUMSFELD/NO BUSH Presidential Campaign Button, 2004; 6477.BT0202; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign Button, 1988; 6477.BT0203; Items: 1 (Box 21)
  - Anti-Giuliani Campaign Button, 2007; 6477.BT0204; Items: 1 (Box 21)
    Candidate: Giuliani, Rudy
  - Abrams Campaign, 6477.BT0205; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Abrams, Bob
  - Agran Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0206; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Agran, Larry
  - Albetta for State Senate Campaign, 6477.BT0207; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Albetta, Michael
  - Anderson Presidential Campaign, 1980; 6477.BT0208; Items: 4 (Box 24)
  - Andrews Campaign for Manhattan Borough President, 1989; 6477.BT0209; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Andrews, Earl Election: 1989
  - Anthony Campaign for Congressman, 1990; 6477.BT0212; Items: (Box 24)
    Election: 1990
  - Bellamy Campaign for Mayor, 1985; 6477.BT0210; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bellamy, Carol
    Election: 1985
  - Bentsen Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0211; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bentsen, Lloyd
  - Biaggi Campaign for Mayor, 1973; 6477.BT0213; Items: 3 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Biaggi, Mario
    Election: 1973
  - Blinken Campaign for Senate, 1990; 6477.BT0214; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Blinken, Alan
  - Blomquist Campaign for Governor, 1992; 6477.BT0215; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Blomquist, Tom
  - Bloom Campaign for Governor, 1958 or 1962; 6477.BT0216; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bloom, Jeremiah
    Election: 1958 or 1962
  - Bradley Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0217; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bradley, Bill
  - Brown Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0218; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Brown, Jerry
  - Bryan/Stevenson Presidential Campaign, 1900; 6477.BT0219; Items:1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bryan/Stevenson
  - Bush Presidential Campaign, 1980; 6477.BT0220; Items: 2 (Box 24)
  - Bush/Quayle Presidential Campaign and Inauguration Buttons, 1988 and 1992; 6477.BT0221; Items: 21 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bush, George and Quayle, Dan
  - Bush Campaign for Senate, ca. 1950's; 6477.BT0222; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Bush, Prescott
    Election: ca. 1950's
  - Buckley for Senate, ca. 1970's; 6477.BT0223; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Buckley, James
  - Carey Campaign for Governor, 1974; 6477.BT0225; Items: 1 (Box 24)
  - Carter/Mondale Presidential Campaigns, 1976 and 1980; 6477.BT0224; Items: 5 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Carter, James and Mondale
    Election: 1976 and 1980
  - Chisholm Presidential Campaign, 1972; 6477.BT0226; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Chisholm, Shirley
  - Clinton/Gore Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0228; Items: 10 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Clinton, Bill and Gore, Al
  - Commoner/Harris Presidential Campaign, 1980; 6477.BT0229; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Commoner, Barry and Harris, La Donna
  - Connally Presidential Campaign, 1980; 6477.BT02; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Connally, John
  - Crowley Campaign for Assembly, 1988; 6477.BT0227; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Crowley, Joseph
  - Cuomo, Cuomo/Lundine Campaigns, 1990 and 1992; 6477.BT0231; Items: 10 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Cuomo, Mario and Lundine
    Election: 1990 Governor, 1992 President
  - D'Amato Campaign for Senate, ca. 1980's; 6477.BT0232; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: D'Amato, Alfonso
  - Dewey/Warren Presidential Campaign, 1948; 6477.BT0233; Items: 3 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Dewey, Thomas and Warren, Earl
    Election: 1948
  - Dietl Campaign for Congress, 1986; 6477.BT0234; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Dietl, Richard
    Election: 1986
  - Dinkins for Mayor, 1989; 6477.BT0235; Items: 8 (Box 24)
    Election: 1989
  - Dole Presidential Campaign, 1988 and 1996; 6477.BT0236; Items: 3 (Box 24)
    Election: 1988, 1996
  - du Pont Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0237; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: du Pont, Pete
  - Dukakis/Bentsen Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0243; Items: 17 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Dukakis, Michael and Bentsen
  - Dyson Campaign for Senate, 1986; 6477.BT0238; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Dyson, John
  - Eisenhower Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0239; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Eisenhower, Dwight
  - Foley Campaign for Congress, ca. 1980's; 6477.BT0240; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Foley, Tom
  - Forbes Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0241; Items: (Box 24)
    Candidate: Forbes
  - Ford/Dole Presidential Campaign, 1976; 6477.BT0242; Items: 2 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Ford, Gerald and Dole, Bob
  - Fulani Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0244; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Fulani, Lenora
  - Gephardt Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0245; Items: 2 (Box 24)
  - Gerson Campaign for Delegate, 6477.BT0246; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Gerson, Sophie
  - Giuliani Campaign, 6477.BT0337; Items: (Box 24)
  - Glenn Presidential Campaign, 1984; 6477.BT047; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Glenn, John
  - Goldwater/Miller Presidential Campaign, 1964; 6477.BT0248; Items: 3 (Box 24)
  - Goodman Campaign for Senate, 6477.BT0249; Items: 3 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Goodman, Roy
  - Gordon Campaign for Senate, 6477.BT0250; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Gordon, Mike
  - Gore Presidential Campaign and Senate, 1988 and 1992; 6477.BT0255; Items: 8 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Gore, Albert
    Election: 1988, 1992
  - Gramm Presidential Campaign, 1996; 6477.BT0251; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Gramm, Phil
  - Grannis for Assembly, 6477.BT0252; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Grannis, Pete
  - Gregory Presidential Campaign, 1968; 6477.BT0253; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Gregory, Dick
  - Greitzer Campaign for Council, ca. 1990; 6477.BT0254; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Greitzer, Carol
  - Haig Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0256; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Haig, Al
  - Harding Presidential Campaign, 1920; 6477.BT0257; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Harding, Warren G.
  - Harkin Presidential Campaign, 1992; 6477.BT0262; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Harkin, Tom
  - Hart Presidential Campaign, 1984 or 1988; 6477.BT0258; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Hart, Gary
    Election: 1984 or 1988
  - Heinz Campaign for Senate, ca. 1976; 6477.BT0259; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Heinz, John
    Election: ca. 1976
  - Hirsch Campaign for Congress, 6477.BT0260; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Hirsch, George
  - Hirschfeld Campaign for Lt. Governor, 1986; 6477.BT0261; Items: 1 (Box 24)
    Candidate: Hirschfeld, Abe
  - Holtzman Campaign for Congress, 1980; 6477.BT0263; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Holtzman, Liz
  - Hoover Presidential Campaign, 1928; 6477.BT0264; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Election: 1928
  - Humphrey/Muskie Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0266; Items: 5 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Humphrey
  - Innis Congress Campaign, 6477.BT0265; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Innis, Roy
  - Jackson Presidential Campaign, 1988; 6477.BT0267; Items: (Box 25)
  - Javits Campaign, 1968; 6477.BT0268; Items: 2 (Box 25)
  - Johnson/Humphrey Presidential Campaign, 1964; 6477.BT0269; Items: 4 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Johnson
  - Katz Assembly Campaign, 6477.BT0270; Items: 1 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Katz, Harvey
  - Kefauver Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0271; Items: 1 (Box 25)
  - Kemp Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0277; Items: 2 (Box 25)
    Candidate: Kemp, Jack
  - Kennedy Presidential Campaign, 6477.BT0272; Items: 2 (Box 25)
  - Kennedy Presidential Campaign, 1968; 6477.BT0273; Items: 2 (Box 25)